puzzledragonx.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy | Puzzle & Dragons Database

| 

## Introduction  
  
---  
Puzzle Dragon X ( PDX ) is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. PDX takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

PDX may amend this policy from time to time without notice to you, you can review the most current version of the privacy statement at any time at: <http://www.puzzledragonx.com/en/privacy.asp>  
  
## Information Collection  
  
PDX collects personally identifiable information when you register for a PDX account. When you register with PDX, we ask for your email address, gender, timezone, and ingame details. You may also choose to provide optional details, such as location or personal comments. PDX allows each member to upload one photo. PDX reserves the right to reject or remove any photos that it deems objectionable or inappropriate for public viewing. Once you register with PDX, you will be assigned a unique member ID and sign in to our services.

PDX uses your information for the general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, and to contact you about new update. We collect this data so that we may provide you with content that we think may interest you and display it according to your preferences. Since the service may depend on some advertising revenue, PDX will display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on PDX. If we change the way we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail.   
  
## Cookies  
  
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

PDX uses its own cookies for accessing your information when you "Login", so that we can provide you with customized content. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of PDX services.   
  
## Information Sharing  
  
PDX agrees will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. In some cases, PDX has partnered with a third party to provide an additional service or feature to the community site and may share member information with those parties. PDX may send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of PDX to provide a service to you, protect and defend the rights or property of PDX, or we find that your actions on our web sites violate the PDX Terms of Service, or any of our usage guidelines for specific services. If we change the way we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you by e-mail.   
  
## Update Your Account Information and Preferences  
  
PDX gives you the ability to edit your PDX Account Information at any time. Your PDX Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.   
  
## Questions or Suggestions  
  
If you have questions or suggestions, please don't hesitate to contact us.
